export const onboardingCards = [
  {
    question: 'What are the success criteria for passing probation period?',
    answer: `
      - Good feedback on the project
      - Fullfilled past project & skills
      - Passed onboarding modules
      - Passed English assessment
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Describe the process of onboarding junior',
    answer: `
      Onboarding is aimed at helping employees to adapt to a diverse EPAM environment with its various tools and processes;
      to help with transition to new roles and responsibilities as smooth as possible. <br />
      Since it's a junior developer he or she will need more help than more senior dev. Mostly junior will need assistance in process, personal development topics.
      If it's project onboarding need to pay attention to the project specific and explain junior architecture, technologies that are used on the project.
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'What should newcomer do or not do in order not to fail probation?',
    answer: `
       Newcomer should complete all action items that were discussed on intro meeting, should follow EPAM culture and processes, has a good perfomance
       on the project.
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'What will you do if newcomer has inappropriate behavior?',
    answer: `
      First of all needed to specify what's inappropriate behavior. The best way to figure it out is a conversation with a problem person.
      And just ask why are you doing this and for which reason. Maybe there is factors that leads to this behavior.
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'While onboarding employees, do you have onboarding plan?',
    answer: `No. I am providing some set of criterias that should be done during probation period ( if it's a new employee ) like passing all modules
     on onboarding portal, passing English assessment, past projects etc. Also, gathering feedbacks from the project is important`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Who and how should be involved in employee adaptation?',
    answer: `Resource Manager, HR, project team`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is responsible for adaptation results?',
    answer: `Employee, manager, project`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Which areas do you cover in scope of adaptation of newcomer?',
    answer: `How newcomer feels in the company, is there any help needed, project adaptation ( how he was accepted by the team )`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Project onboarding of junior and senior. What additional actions you need to perform, information additional to share for senior that it not required to junior?',
    answer: `It depend on the project, but it could be information about architecture stuff, CI/CD, customer information. Senior needs more high level
    understading about the project to see the whole picture to provide some improvements in the future.`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'What are criteria of successful onboarding? ',
    answer: `
      - Employee understands what internal processes as much as he/she need to complete daily duties
      - Employee has a good performance on the project, gets good feedback from the team members
      `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Prolongation of probation period, any cases? or dismissal during probation?',
    answer: `
      - Prolongation - when employee hasn't working on the project enough time and there is no possible to get full feedback; exeptional/emergency cases; <br />
      - Dismissal. Bad performance on the project, violation of EPAM culture, inappropriate behaviour.
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'In what cases would you close probation faster?',
    answer: `Employee finished all probation tasks; got good feedback on the project.`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'How would you know the onboarding is completed?',
    answer: `Employee understands how company works, how local processes is working; has a good performance on the project.`,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'Describe typical action items from onboarding to the project?',
    answer: `
      - Introduce newcomer to the team
      - Invite newcomer into all required meetings ( dailies etc. )
      - Provide general overview of the project ( what the purpose of the project, what are we developing )
      - Provide an overview of project code base, provide project documentation if possible.
      - Start with small tasks, for example with some small bug ) to get aquinted with the code
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  },
  {
    question: 'What\'s the difference between onboarding and adaptation? your steps as RM in these processes?',
    answer: `
      As for me, onboarding it's more formal process in the company. Adaptation is more about personal feeling of the employee inside the company.
    `,
    category: "onboarding"
  }
]
